[{"answer": "To her very famous friends.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Right, Chunk?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, you know what.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "For what?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Guilty.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "How did you feel about that?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I wouldn't have -- I don't know that I would have bumped you for -- no, I don't bump people.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Would you have done that?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "For President Obama?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, this isn't a real circumstance that you're talking about.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "You'd turn down the president for me?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Where you've been cruelly bounceful (ph).", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "With you?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Of Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "I think it's a pretty bunch of a hot mess.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "What do you think of the whole crazy Sheen circus?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "ORGAN: You've been of a hot mess?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "You did.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "I got here on time, didn't I?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "I know it's weird --", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "And we just thought, you know?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "No, I won't touch your genitals.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Any of that planned for me this evening?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "You haven't read it?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, obviously you grab people's BlackBerries and you just send appalling stuff to all their contacts.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "ANDLER: It is.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Is it funny?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Well, like I'll send out, you know, e-mails from people on staff to their friends and family.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "What do you write?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Has it damaged you, do you think?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Does it make you seek out an audience, looking for some bit of approval?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Do -- yes, I do.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "You still do stand-up?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Do you remember dying on your back side?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "The worst feeling in the entire universe is to bomb.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "What is that like for a stand-up?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Could you handle that?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Chuy, want to say hi to Norman?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "You look very beautiful.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Probably not, right?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Well, don't we all, darling?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Occasionally.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Do you watch your show?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Don't you think?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Well, she also -- her mother passed away.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Why is she so obnoxious?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Is there a difference between ego and narcissism?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Well, if you're constantly -- you can care what people think about you, but you shouldn't only be serving yourself.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "What's the difference, do you think?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Well, he's a great life.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Who's going to hire him?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Life doesn't get much better, does it?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "You can.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "What is the -- I presume I can ask you anything, right?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Much-discussed and speculated on love life?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "I don't -- first of all I have to get his name because -- remind me.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Who are you currently having sex with?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "It's that good, huh?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "That sounds familiar actually.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "(INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "I'm just surprised --", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "We all know who I'm dating, what do you want me to talk about?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "This woman that tells every shocking detail about her love, sex life and this that, suddenly goes all coy on me.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "His underwear?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "We do.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Do we?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, I've learned to respect somebody else's privacy.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "You've learned about privacy, haven't you?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "We dated.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Tell me what was the truth of you and old 50?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Nothing -- you know he's a very sweet and nice guy, but obviously -- I was just sampling, kind of the atmosphere and seeing what was out there.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "And what happened?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "He's fun.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "And what was he like to go out with?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "He's not what you imagine him to be, isn't he?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Well, I don't really like gifts from rappers in general, since I'm not a hooker, but no.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I've returned gifts, but I've returned gifts to plenty of people.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Is there a semblance of truth there?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "He's the female version of Ryan Seacrest.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "How do you feel about being called the male -- the female version of Ryan Seacrest?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Ryan Seacrest?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Well, it expires soon.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "What has happened with your contract?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "No, that's how much it costs to rent me for the night.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Well, what are you worth?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Well, then you know what you're worth.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "What is -- I am ruthless when it comes to business, but was it your worth?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "ANDLER: Why are you -- shut up.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "How?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Because it's gross.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Why are you being so coy again?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "I like vacations a lot.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "How would you like to spend this money you don't want to talk about?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm very generous.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Are you generous?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "I have no patience.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "What's the worst?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "I've crossed the line into annoying several times.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Does that make you naturally mischievous bordering on annoying?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Did you hear when I just said?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Vodka?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Wait.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Are you just a compulsive liar?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "I'm -- you know.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "What are kind of girl are you?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "I'm a pain in the ass.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "I want to hear it from your lips?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "I think it's OK.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "But in quite a good way?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Two of the guys -- both of the people I dated.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "With who?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Maybe.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Is one the current one?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "Not yet?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "My ex-boyfriend Ted.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Who was the other one?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Is he?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "Yes, I will.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Will you tell him hello for me?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "Anything you want to say?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Do you think I mince my words?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "I don't think it really matters.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Is it wise to dip your pen in company ink?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Because it's fun and it gives us something to watch.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "Well, that's an interesting question as well.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "How have you resisted getting married?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "I wouldn't say that, no.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "But do you have a little part of you that dreams wistfully of a fairy tale wedding?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "That's what I'm getting at.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Can you believe it?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "What marriage?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Are you having twins?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "No, not that I know of.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "You're not pregnant?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "Would you like children?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "I hope not.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 728, "question": "Never going to happen?", "qSentId": 727}, {"answer": "Because I'm not somebody that wants to be a mother.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "Because I think you would be a good mother.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "Like a little Chelsea to play with?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "I guess everyone that I work with.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "Really makes you laugh?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "I think both.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "What was your reaction?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "People who are so nervous.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 826, "question": "What's the worst type of guest for you?", "qSentId": 825}, {"answer": "Well, I'm interested in politics.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 835, "question": "If you were doing a more serious thing, what kind of issues really get you going?", "qSentId": 834}, {"answer": "ANDLER: Well, Boehner is ridiculous.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 841, "question": "Any politicians that you just can't stand?", "qSentId": 840}, {"answer": "That's not a serious person.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 852, "question": "Are you a fan of hers?", "qSentId": 851}, {"answer": "That's getting interesting.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 858, "question": "President Trump?", "qSentId": 857}, {"answer": "He is way ahead in all the polls", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 861, "question": "Is he?", "qSentId": 860}, {"answer": "Well, hopefully our minds, because that would be ridiculous if Donald Trump became president.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 864, "question": "What else do we have to go on?", "qSentId": 863}, {"answer": "Yes, it would.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 866, "question": "Would it be ridiculous?", "qSentId": 865}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 872, "question": "Was that really his fault?", "qSentId": 871}, {"answer": "Well, not entirely.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 874, "question": "Do you think so?", "qSentId": 873}, {"answer": "No, I think he was very irresponsible.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 877, "question": "Would anybody have been governor of California in that financial crisis and not caught a big cold?", "qSentId": 876}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 886, "question": "Did you vote for Obama?", "qSentId": 885}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 888, "question": "Would you again?", "qSentId": 887}, {"answer": "That wasn't really -- that wasn't the question.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 891, "question": "Well, I think it takes a long time to get things accomplished?", "qSentId": 890}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 906, "question": "Have you met him?", "qSentId": 905}, {"answer": "He asked me where Chewy was actually.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 908, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 907}, {"answer": "He did.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 910, "question": "He didn't?", "qSentId": 909}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 923, "question": "What does the future hold for Chelsea Handler Incorporated, this burgeoning empire?", "qSentId": 922}, {"answer": "You don't have to be so touchy about it.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 940, "question": "What kind of question is that?", "qSentId": 939}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 945, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 944}, {"answer": "I'm just talking about my feelings.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 947, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 946}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 951, "question": "Where does this empire go next?", "qSentId": 950}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 956, "question": "Do you want to stay there?", "qSentId": 955}, {"answer": "ANDLER: I'm producing a bunch of TV shows.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 964, "question": "Choose any job in the world?", "qSentId": 963}, {"answer": "Oh -- I mean -- well, the easiest thing that people -- people can write about me, because I'm so forthcoming about my life and that I like Belvedere, you know, and that I'm not a stickler for a lot of rules in my personal life or that kind of thing.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 970, "question": "What's been the most ridiculous thing you read about yourself?", "qSentId": 969}, {"answer": "We don't -- no, we don't.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 979, "question": "Ever do that?", "qSentId": 978}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 982, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 981}, {"answer": "ANDLER: We go over to her house, hang out.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 998, "question": "What do you do when you go out together?", "qSentId": 997}, {"answer": "You could have a conversation with her.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 1011, "question": "She wouldn't be real?", "qSentId": 1010}, {"answer": "I would say the best moment of my life would be when my \"Chelsea Chelsea Bang Bang\" book came out last year, and they called to tell me that I was number one on the list --", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 1016, "question": "If you could relive one moment in your life in five minutes to live, what would it be?", "qSentId": 1015}, {"answer": "On \"the New York Times\" best seller, but my other two books were number two and three.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 1018, "question": "On \"the New York Times\" best seller?", "qSentId": 1017}, {"answer": "Because I have no business writing books.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 1030, "question": "Why would you say?", "qSentId": 1029}, {"answer": "I don't think that we can say 100 percent.", "docId": "110510pmt", "aSentId": 1046, "question": "Do you both 100 percent believe she's still alive or do you have to believe that?", "qSentId": 1045}]